thefacegamer.com 2017-11-30

# The Facegamer’s Privacy Policy – The Facegamer

_Last Updated: April 23, 2010_

## Introduction:

I really didn’t want to have to make one of these, but I don’t want to be sued either. I just wanna blog. And dance. Maybe dance while blogging. Can I blog and dance and harvest my Farmville crops? Anyway…

The following privacy notice applies to The Facegamer web site. I may change or update this policy from time to time, and I will notify you of any changes by changing the “last updated” notice thingie at the top of this policy document, thingie. Any updated policy shall be effected immediately after it is posted. Thingie.

## In regards to Ads:

The Facegamer is a one-girl show, and is really not interested in your personal information. You should know that I use third-party advertising companies (Google, etc) to serve ads when you visit my website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you.

It’s really nothing to worry about it, but if you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about having this information used by these companies, �[please follow this link.](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)

It’s really fine because it shows you ads that are sometimes *actually* related to what I’m talking about. And I like that you can opt-out if you still are uncomfortable about it.

## Activity:

The Facegamer may ask you for some personal information, including your email-address, for certain activies on The Facegamer, such as uploading pictures or posting comments.

Posting is completely optional, and you can enjoy reading The Facegamer without disclosing personal information.

The Facegamer doesn’t use your email address or other personally identifiable information to send commercial or marketing messages without your consent or except as part of a program or feature for which you will have the ability to opt-in or opt-out. I may, however, use your email address without further consent for non-marketing or administrative purposes (such as customer service purposes). If you ask me for help in a game, I might also use your email address to find your profile in Facebook so I can help you out.

## Cookies; IP Logs:

The Facegamer uses cookies, and not the chocolate chip kind, to (a) store information so that you will not have to re-enter it during your visit; (b) provide custom, personalized content and information (the ads mentioned above, for example);(c) monitor aggregate metrics such as total number of visitors, pages viewed, etc etc etc. I really just want to know what you like and what you hated, so I can do the good stuff more; (d)track your entries, submission and status in promotions, sweepstakes and contests.

Special Note About Google Advertising

Any advertisements served by Google, Inc., and affiliated companies may be controlled using cookies. These cookies allow Google to display ads based on your visits to this site and other sites that use Google advertising services. Learn how to opt out of Google’s cookie usage. As mentioned above, any tracking done by Google through cookies and other mechanisms is subject to Google’s own privacy policies.

About Google advertising: What is the DoubleClick DART cookie? The DoubleClick DART cookie is used by Google in the ads served on publisher websites displaying AdSense for content ads. When users visit an AdSense publisher�s website and either view or click on an ad, a cookie may be dropped on that end user�s browser. The data gathered from these cookies will be used to help AdSense publishers better serve and manage the ads on their site(s) and across the web. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy.

Again, you can read about that stuff here: �<http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html>

## Your Choices; Opt-out:

1\. You may, of course, decline to submit personally identifiable information through The Facegamer, in which you can still take advantage of information, �follow picture links, etc. You could probably even give false information and I wouldn’t know or care, to be honest, as long as you’re not hurting me or anyone else that uses The Facegamer. If you don’t provide information, The Facegamer may not be able to provide certain services to you, such as allowing you to participate in discussions in the comment sections of each post.

2) You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser to decline cookies in the browser settings if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to sign in or use other website deatures or services that depend on cookies. If you choose to accept cookies, your browser may allow you to delete cookies that you have accepted at a later date.

## In conclusion:

In a nutshell, anything that my website, The Facegamer, collects is only used to show you ads that you might find useful, and to allow you to interact with the website itself and other viewers. I am really not interested in pissing anyone off, and if I did, let me know so I can fix it and make it right.

Be Sociable, Share!

  *
